

JENNY ADAMS

WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

A hard-working front-end developer, equipped with industry standard languages, experience from two of Wellington's top web agencies, and a passion for positive change.

Contact

- iennyadamsnz@gmail.com
- **2** 027 556 9938
- inkedin.com/in/jennyadamsnz
- jennyadamsnz.github.ic

(+) Interests

- Reading
- ★ Travelling
- X DIY
- : New Technologies



Employment

■ NOV 2017 - PRESENT

Heyday

Front-End Developer

Building and maintaining commercial websites of notable brands built on SilverStripe. I did most of the Front-End work for barnardosearlylearning.org.nz and regularly maintain wellingtonzoo.com, drive.govt.nz, summerset.co.nz, powershop.co.nz, whittakers.co.nz, bankomb.org.nz, protectivesecurity.govt.nz, garageproject.co.nz & mmnz.co.nz

MAY 2017 - NOV 2017

Springload

Junior Front-End Developer

A fixed-term contract, primarily to maintain Kiwibank's legacy website while it was replaced. I also created email templates & helped create a pattern library for Xero's staff intranet.

AUG 2016 - MAY 2017

AdviceUnlimited

Web Development & Design

Working as part of a small team to build quick and affordable websites for small to medium sized businesses using Squarespace.



Education

MAY 2016 - MAY 2017

Yoobee School of Design Diploma of Web Development

An introdutory course to front-end and back-end coding using HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Laravel, Wordpress.

2008 - 2010

Victoria University of Wellington Bachelor of Arts

Majoring in International Relations & Media Studies



Skills

LANGUAGES HTML5, CSS3, SASS, LESS, JS,

PHP, Python, Django

VERSION CONTROL Git, Node.js, Gulp, Grunt, & TOOLS Vagrant, Docker

SOFTWARE Invision, Sketch, Photoshop,

Zeplin, Jira, Harvest, Campaign

Monitor, Sequel Pro

CMSs SilverStripe, Laravel, Wordpress,

Wagtail, Squarespace